[{"id": "5906835cff9c0647b50a80a6", "question": "Alec Baldwin started hosting which ABC show on June 26, 2016?", "answer": "Match Game", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ed7", "question": "The journey in Roald Dahl's \"James and the Giant Peach\" ends with the peach impaled on what?", "answer": "The Empire State Building", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2a1", "question": "After the Civil War, which Union general became the first president of the NRA?", "answer": "Ambrose Burnside", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339069", "question": "Who is the Greek Goddess of witchcraft and magic?", "answer": "Hecate", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c359", "question": "On which planet did the spacecraft Venus 8 land in 1972?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b95c", "question": "The Purple Heart is awarded for which reason?", "answer": "For wounds received by enemy action while on active service", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe73513eec85e375820b243", "question": "Who was President John F. Kennedy's Attorney General?", "answer": "His brother Robert F. Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe25a30658e585fda9cfa44", "question": "What does the term \"au gratin\" mean when it comes to cooking?", "answer": "Covered with browned crust, often breadcrumbs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b89e", "question": "In what sport do the contestants throw salt before the contest?", "answer": "Sumo wrestling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a28a", "question": "Who was the lead singer of the band Motorhead?", "answer": "Lemmy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6d6", "question": "What city is located across the Columbia River from the city of Vancouver?", "answer": "Portland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe93d646bd93ce3a4e5f6b5", "question": "Which is the windiest planet in our solar system?", "answer": "Neptune", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb2c", "question": "In what country is Absolut vodka made?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b34a", "question": "Which real person took a name meaning Man of Steel?", "answer": "Joseph Stalin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aea4", "question": "Which British Prime Minister had the nickname dizzy?", "answer": "Benjamin Disraelli", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59cdb45f65ff7d326b622a86", "question": "What is the fear of glass known as?", "answer": "Nelophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338eb9", "question": "What Broadway musical featured the song \"Gary, Indiana\"?", "answer": "The Music Man", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c33", "question": "Which actor played the main protagonist in the TV show \"Twin Peaks\"?", "answer": "Kyle MacLachlan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391aa", "question": "Who played James Bond in the 1971 film \"Diamonds Are Forever\"?", "answer": "Sean Connery", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c455", "question": "What creature takes its name from Aboriginal words for \"no drink\"?", "answer": "Koala", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febb5af7e83c707845b211f", "question": "What's the word for when you can't remember a word?", "answer": "Lethologica", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cefc0ec948005ec986edce1", "question": "Who is the eighth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Choerry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339251", "question": "What band performed the Bond theme song \"A View to a Kill\"?", "answer": "Duran Duran", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339db7", "question": "In what movie does Walter Brennan annoy people with the question \"Was you ever bit by a dead bee\"?", "answer": "To Have and Have Not", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4aa", "question": "Which country were the 1948 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a166", "question": "Who played Sarah Conner in 1984 film \"The Terminator\"?", "answer": "Linda Hamilton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c93", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Dillon, Texas?", "answer": "Friday Night Lights", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e94d0b65ea27d7a1303aed2", "question": "In a standard deck of cards, which of the face cards are the only ones whose hair is colored in a deck of playing cards?", "answer": "Jacks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bada", "question": "What brand of cat food was advertised by Morris the Cat?", "answer": "9 Lives", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb59a85dad637d903c8813", "question": "In which Alaskan town do almost all residents live in the same building?", "answer": "In the small town of Whittier, Alaska, almost all residents live in the same building \u2014 a property called Begich Towers", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60062cc2c9d816e292245c2e", "question": "To which artistic movement does Paul Gauguin's The Yellow Christ belong?", "answer": "The Yellow Christ\u00a0is a painting that depicts the crucifixion. The techniques used in this painting are typical of\u00a0cloisonnism.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b67", "question": "What Disney cartoon character originally had the name Mortimer?", "answer": "Mickey Mouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133921c", "question": "What city did the band U2 form in?", "answer": "Dublin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca4b", "question": "What bird has the biggest wingspan?", "answer": "Albatross", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3af", "question": "Where in the United States is coffee grown?", "answer": "Hawaii and California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133928f", "question": "What object lands in Donnie Darko's bedroom?", "answer": "A jet engine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c5c2877e98cb977789b3", "question": "The \"Khyber Pass\" connects what two countries?", "answer": "Afghanistan and Pakistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c012", "question": "What did a Cordwainer make?", "answer": "Shoes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b446", "question": "What year did Joseph Merrick, also known as Elephant Man, die?", "answer": "1890", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339166", "question": "What is the secret identity of Don Vito Corleone?", "answer": "The Godfather", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c47f", "question": "What are baby sharks known as?", "answer": "Pups", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd30", "question": "Where was the first FIFA World Cup held?", "answer": "Uruguay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a41d", "question": "What is the modern day equivalent of Dutch Guiana?", "answer": "Suriname", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a4d974f08b8581f80b092a9", "question": "What country was host to the \u201c2017 World Expo\u201d?", "answer": "Kazakhstan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4e1", "question": "What do you get when you mix scotch, sweet vermouth and angostura bitters?", "answer": "A Rob Roy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb4", "question": "How old was General Tom Thumb when he joined P. T. Barnum's circus in 1843?", "answer": "5", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e6b25cfb6c85e9e634ff3d", "question": "Which region of France do Germans call Lothringen?", "answer": "Lorraine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c88d", "question": "What does the Holmes and Rahe scale measure?", "answer": "Stress caused by life events", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fde5107c6c6b019850c9a8c", "question": "Mariner IV sent the first pictures of which planet back to Earth?", "answer": "Mars", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "590680bdff9c0647b50a808e", "question": "Which character did Anton Yelchin portray in the Star Trek film series reboot, prior to his death in 2016?", "answer": "Pavel Chekov", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e7", "question": "What is the longest one syllable word in the English language?", "answer": "Screeched", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0b6", "question": "Maraschino is a liqueur made from what fruit?", "answer": "Marasca cherries", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339779", "question": "Which original song from Titanic won an Oscar in 1997?", "answer": "My Heart Will Go On", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b122", "question": "What was the two-word code name for Woodward and Bernstein's secret Watergate source?", "answer": "Deep Throat", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015f7c9fe83fe1f2a824c26", "question": "Who was the UK\u2019s second woman Prime Minister?", "answer": "Theresa May", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389d9", "question": "What book does each girl receive as a Christmas present at the start of \"Little Women\"?", "answer": "The Pilgrim's Progress", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb1", "question": "In 1926, the funeral of what silent movie star attracted a crowd of nearly 100,000 people to view the remains?", "answer": "Rudolph Valentino", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc854c9abc30a8194e188aa", "question": "Who wrote the book \"The Perfect Storm\"?", "answer": "Sebastian Junger", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c866", "question": "Who invented the lightning rod, though he refused to patent it?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a476", "question": "What African country was formerly known as Northern Rhodesia?", "answer": "Zambia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339913", "question": "What California city was the setting for the TV series \u201cEight is Enough\u201d?", "answer": "Sacramento", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea47c3ff048f679a45abad", "question": "What strangely named type of mackerel is also known as an Ono in Hawaii?", "answer": "Wahoo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcfc", "question": "In France, what is called \"pain perdu\"?", "answer": "French toast", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4e90906d333868d34d750", "question": "What country were cars invented in?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecdab1ec223966ae8f88eb", "question": "Who is the only \"Top Gun\" actor who didn't vomit while in the fighter jets?", "answer": "Anthony Edwards", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909cb2dbb53d1af658864d6", "question": "Who wrote the 1994 novel \"Inspector Proby\u2019s Christmas\"?", "answer": "John Gano", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60078af70eee65b76b9f2662", "question": "Kleenex was invented to serve what purpose during World War I?", "answer": "Kleenex was originally invented for use as a gas mask filter. Kimberly-Clark remarketed Kleenex in 1924 as a makeup remover.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4fa", "question": "What two US state names end with the letter Y?", "answer": "Kentucky and New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133888d", "question": "What did the Seven Dwarfs do for a living?", "answer": "They were miners", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58bb3522e368446ca7bd684f", "question": "What chemical reaction during roasting is chiefly responsible for giving green coffee beans their flavor?", "answer": "Maillard Reaction", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd6a3126c0f9723ab15cb49", "question": "What was the first department store?", "answer": "Harding, Howell and Company Grand Fashionable Magazine", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf50", "question": "What is the fear of being tickled by feathers known as?", "answer": "Pteronophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1ea", "question": "What profession did George Constanza often pretend to be in the sitcom \"Seinfeld\"?", "answer": "Architect", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339feb", "question": "Queen and Duran Duran both had drummers with what name?", "answer": "Roger Taylor", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390a1", "question": "What is Demeter the god of?", "answer": "Harvest and agriculture", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee0", "question": "What literary villain died during a struggle at Reichenbach Falls?", "answer": "Professor Moriarty", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a182", "question": "Turbo Terrific is a car featured in which cartoon?", "answer": "Wacky Races", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393be", "question": "Who played the role of Cirus the Virus in the movie \"Con Air\"?", "answer": "John Malkovich", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c9a", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Melonville?", "answer": "SCTV", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c972", "question": "What colour are shelled pistachio nuts?", "answer": "Green", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af5f", "question": "In addition to his more historic crime, Lee Harvey Oswald was charged with killing what policeman?", "answer": "J. D. Tippit", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fede34d6ce05a3942286dd1", "question": "Who was originally cast as Holly Golightly in \"Breakfast at Tiffany\u2019s\"?", "answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8ba", "question": "A gift of china is given to celebrate the anniversary of how many years of marriage?", "answer": "20", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cefc278948005ec986edcea", "question": "What US state is Helena the capital of?", "answer": "Montana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b813", "question": "What is the Jewish New Year called?", "answer": "Rosh Hashanah", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec84b2ec223966ae8f8801", "question": "Which NFL team has the longest season-ticket waiting list?", "answer": "Green Bay Packers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bb357722627b8fe95581be4", "question": "Brisbane is the capital of which Australian state?", "answer": "Queensland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5907214c3745b36be73039f6", "question": "What is the name of the popular Christmas song that Will\u2019s dad composed in the 2002 film \"About a Boy\"?", "answer": "Santa\u2019s Super Sleigh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5db03e6caa1c9af2684d79a4", "question": "What is the common name for CH3COOH?", "answer": "Acetic acid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393f9", "question": "What actor/singer played the role of Right Arm in the 1997 movie \"The Fifth Element\"?", "answer": "Tricky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea39f9ff048f679a45ab29", "question": "What element is named after the Greek word for green?", "answer": "Chlorine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca07", "question": "The first integral of acceleration gives us what?", "answer": "Velocity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af78", "question": "Which US president is buried in Mount Vernon, Virginia?", "answer": "George Washington", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adc5", "question": "Which maritime explorer gave the Pacific Ocean its name?", "answer": "Ferdinand Magellan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b19c", "question": "What dog breed was the official 1972 Summer Olympics mascot?", "answer": "Dachshund", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab2f", "question": "Which ocean is the region of Melanesia located in?", "answer": "Pacific", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b17", "question": "Who wielded a sword named Excalibur?", "answer": "King Arthur", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133922f", "question": "What fruity brand of cigarettes, a Quentin Tarantino trademark made yet another appearance in \"Pulp Fiction\"?", "answer": "Red Apple", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937eee908d98002fdd633da", "question": "What is 2000 in Roman Numerals?", "answer": "MM", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c33e", "question": "How long does it take the moon to revolve around the Earth, to the nearest day?", "answer": "27", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c793", "question": "What part of the cheetah does not have any spots?", "answer": "The belly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7d5", "question": "In the standard Monopoly game, how much money do you collect for finishing second in a beauty contest?", "answer": "$10", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0ce", "question": "Who directed the film \"Ordinary People\"?", "answer": "Robert Redford", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b6a", "question": "In the movie \"Jerry Maguire\", Jerry sings along to what Tom Petty song on his car radio?", "answer": "Free Fallin'", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc79", "question": "What company's famous plaid pattern is called \"novacheck\"?", "answer": "Burberry's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6017378544491cbd7c5a178b", "question": "How did the U.S. state Tennessee aquire the nickname, \"The Volunteer State\"?", "answer": "It became known as \"The Volunteer State\" during the War of 1812 due to its prominent role of sending 1,500 volunteer soldiers.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0e5", "question": "Japan signed the term of surrender for WWII aboard which US battleship?", "answer": "USS Missouri", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdda", "question": "Ash Wednesday marks the first day of what?", "answer": "Lent", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0d4", "question": "In what year were Skittles candy first sold in the US?", "answer": "1974", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b0a", "question": "What was the title of the 2005 Bravo reality series which featured Whitney Houston and Bobby Brown?", "answer": "Being Bobby Brown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff14300b0ee8c595b6d39b0", "question": "With what type of quick drawings did a young Claude Monet begin creating art?", "answer": "Caricature", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "597cdaa5e347d002c297e4d5", "question": "What nationality is Yehudi Menuhin?", "answer": "American", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab9a", "question": "The port of Piraeus serves which European capital?", "answer": "Athens", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ba", "question": "Who is the creator of Inspector Morse?", "answer": "Colin Dexter", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59068390ff9c0647b50a80a8", "question": "How many original shows and movies did Netflix release in 2016?", "answer": "45", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600240884be4723ccac22166", "question": "In the film \"The Hunt for Red October,\" Captain Marko Ramius is from what country?", "answer": "Lithuania", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c211", "question": "What year were the first Winter Olympic Games held?", "answer": "1924", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d4", "question": "What TV sitcom's final episode revealed that the previous seasons had all been a dream?", "answer": "Newhart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58c9f7d0b4e2c7fbd389674c", "question": "Who wrote the essay \"A Nice Cup of Tea\"?", "answer": "George Orwell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6010ca970775fa611bce67fb", "question": "What were chopsticks originally used for?", "answer": "Cooking -- Their length made them ideal for reaching deep into boiling pots of water or oil.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a13a", "question": "In the TV series \"The Fall Guy\", who did Lee Majors play?", "answer": "Colt Seavers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b31", "question": "What classic movie's title character's first and middle names were Charles Foster?", "answer": "Citizen Kane", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e72ceb5d0874f1a5e2d1c28", "question": "What country borders both North Korea and Finland?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b7b", "question": "What Soviet dancer defected to the West in 1974, joining the New York City Ballet?", "answer": "Mikhail Baryshnikov", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb59d35dad637d903c8815", "question": "What is the largest county in the United States?", "answer": "San Bernardino County, California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a84a", "question": "In what year did Atlanta become the fifth capital of Georgia?", "answer": "1868", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f40", "question": "What musical instrument does Jack steal from the beanstalk giant?", "answer": "A harp", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febb1137e83c707845b210b", "question": "Which planet was discovered by mathematical prediction before it was directly observed?", "answer": "Neptune", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d8", "question": "What element combines with sodium to make ordinary table salt?", "answer": "Chlorine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a9f", "question": "What US state is the setting for \"The Cleveland Show\"?", "answer": "Virginia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd662c7a5bfecdd737e0848", "question": "What was Princess Diana's title before she married Prince Charles?", "answer": "Lady Diana Spencer", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339155", "question": "What is a platinum record awarded for?", "answer": "An LP selling a million copies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af9d", "question": "Who became King of Spain on General Franco's death?", "answer": "Juan Carlos I", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdc105b469bb8041d07a06d", "question": "What popular holiday beverage contains sugar, milk and eggs?", "answer": "Eggnog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59524772736d4be723796b72", "question": "Approximately 7.5 million of what can be created from a cord of wood?", "answer": "Toothpicks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa7c", "question": "What is the capital of Zimbabwe?", "answer": "Harare", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fefc33a6ce05a3942286f20", "question": "In the film \"Capote\", who played the role of Truman Capote's love interest?", "answer": "Bruce Greenwood", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefa5ea6ce05a3942286ec6", "question": "In the film \"Dragnet,\" who played Sgt. Joe Friday?", "answer": "Dan Aykroyd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389a2", "question": "Who authored 1883's \"The Adventures of Pinocchio\"?", "answer": "Carlo Collodi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f5658733a95c66dc4fe759", "question": "Which number system uses only the symbols 1 and 0?", "answer": "The binary system", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beaa", "question": "What cousin of the glockenspiel was named for its ethereal, \"heavenly\" sound?", "answer": "The celesta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba4b", "question": "What were the Portsmouth Spartans renamed after the team was moved to Detroit?", "answer": "Detroit Lions", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fcc", "question": "What TV show did \"Trapper John, M.D.\" spin off from?", "answer": "M*A*S*H", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a74d", "question": "Which US state is home to the Catskill Mountains?", "answer": "New York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c24a", "question": "How many liters are there in the Impertial gallon?", "answer": "4.5 liters", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b7ffb733a3a814d89068c65", "question": "Who wanted you to \"Shake Your Groove Thing\"?", "answer": "Peaches & Herb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "595643f9803c1f1ebcc4a031", "question": "Ketchup was sold in the 1830\u2019s as what?", "answer": "Medicine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c0a", "question": "What year did Anna Nicole Smith die from a drug overdose?", "answer": "2007", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a082", "question": "On what date did Bob Barker retire from hosting \"The Price is Right\"?", "answer": "June 15, 2007", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcd1", "question": "On what golf course would you find the three tricky holes called the \"Amen Corner\"?", "answer": "Augusta National Golf Club", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c044", "question": "What do you have if you suffer from podobromhidrosis?", "answer": "Smelly feet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cb0b", "question": "What protein is responsible for giving blood its color?", "answer": "Hemoglobin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddf", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"alcohol\"?", "answer": "Arabic", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd66309a5bfecdd737e084b", "question": "What was John Wayne\u2019s last movie?", "answer": "\"The Shootist\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdabc2c0b8cce1e6fda705c", "question": "A pentagram's four lower points symbolize air, fire, water and which other item?", "answer": "Earth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a529", "question": "What city is the capital of the US state Arkansas?", "answer": "Little Rock", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe8b50201dd7bf43be5e7cb", "question": "What is the main ingredient in the British dish laverbread?", "answer": "Seaweed", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5906834bff9c0647b50a80a5", "question": "What TV show, sequel to an ABC sitcom that ended in 1995, was released by Netflix on February 26, 2016?", "answer": "Fuller House", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b979", "question": "What was the fabled city of gold that some 16th century Europeans believed existed in South America?", "answer": "El Dorado", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adce", "question": "At which battle was poison gas first used?", "answer": "Second Battle of Ypres", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60062b98c9d816e292245c20", "question": "Where is the first underwater art museum in the U.S.?", "answer": "Santa Rosa Beach, Florida", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339819", "question": "The I-V-vi-IV chord progression is commonly referred to by what alliterative name?", "answer": "Pop-punk progression", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8f43d01dd7bf43be5e820", "question": "TBD stands for what?", "answer": "To Be Determined", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe733b0eec85e375820b224", "question": "What was Australia's original purpose as a colony?", "answer": "To be a British prison", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5990f369fa5fdd6dd25324da", "question": "Which film producer said \"Anyone who goes to a psychiatrist ought to have his head examined\"?", "answer": "Samuel Goldwyn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a19f", "question": "Who is Homer Simpson's half-brother?", "answer": "Herb Powell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af98453aeb0982ee455954b", "question": "A nonagon is a shape that has how many sides?", "answer": "9", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a532", "question": "The Guggenheim Museum is located in what city?", "answer": "New York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd823ddd0de9af39e9d46b4", "question": "How long did the Pony Express mail service last?", "answer": "18 months", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdfc", "question": "What is the lowest ranking ace in bridge?", "answer": "Clubs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a656", "question": "What US city is known as the \"Cradle of Liberty\"?", "answer": "Boston", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf84", "question": "What is British politician William Hague's middle name?", "answer": "Jefferson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a29", "question": "What is the Oscar statuette holding in its hands?", "answer": "A sword", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015ec49fe83fe1f2a824bfe", "question": "In the United States, 1 May is officially recognized as Loyalty Day. Which American President instituted this holiday?", "answer": "Dwight D. Eisenhower", "category": "history"}, {"id": "594d04f11a1c922dd1ac649f", "question": "What king was murdered by Macbeth?", "answer": "King Duncan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b54c", "question": "What two colours make purple?", "answer": "Red and Blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afa9", "question": "On which island was Napoleon exiled in 1814?", "answer": "Elba", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ec7231757c9fcac0ce7197a", "question": "What horse broke a Triple Crown drought lasting over 30 years?", "answer": "American Pharoah", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b09b", "question": "Who was the first president to have been born after the American Revolution?", "answer": "Martin Van Buren", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe640a8ae7e414034b5aea4", "question": "Which countries participated in the Lobster War?", "answer": "France and Brazil", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c55c", "question": "In what direction do most cyclones whirl in the Southern Hemisphere?", "answer": "Clockwise", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b80f", "question": "What two snacks are mentioned in \"Take Me Out to the Ballgame\"?", "answer": "Peanuts and Cracker Jack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa3893c73aa70ea0b70ad3", "question": "The San Blas Islands are part of which Central American nation?", "answer": "Panama", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b323268bf195a31e15d7390", "question": "What country is directly west of Spain?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afd3", "question": "What was the Boulder Dam renamed to in 1947?", "answer": "Hoover Dam", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e33", "question": "Who is Mia Farrow's mother?", "answer": "Maureen O'Sullivan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339158", "question": "What popular artist sang the words: \"I'm afraid of Americans\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60062ce4c9d816e292245c2f", "question": "Actor James Franco once sold a sculpture made of what?", "answer": "In 2011, a collector paid $10,000 for a \"non-visible\" sculpture titled\u00a0\"Fresh Air\"\u00a0and billed as \"an endless tank of oxygen\".", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e4", "question": "Which popular musician co-wrote the song \"I'm afraid of Americans\" with David Bowie?", "answer": "Brian Eno", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58d474acf8e329de4f87789f", "question": "On what date did Margaret Thatcher assume office as Prime Minister of the United Kingdom?", "answer": "May 4, 1979", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a02b", "question": "In the TV show \"Family Guy\", where did Stewie first meet his archenemy, Bertram?", "answer": "Inside Peter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa3f", "question": "What is the capital of China?", "answer": "Beijing", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ae", "question": "In what US state is Dry Tortugas National Park?", "answer": "Florida", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133964d", "question": "What kind of animal is the title character in the 2003 movie \"Finding Nemo\"?", "answer": "Clownfish", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8d7312b42d4a3561a9f0b", "question": "Prior to joining the revived \u201cTop Gear\u201d TV series in 2003, what year did James May co-host the original \u201cTop Gear\u201d series?", "answer": "1999", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab24", "question": "What island country is located east of Mozambique?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "594a62ba2ebb971c1417fb92", "question": "Which two countries took part in the \"Turbot War\" dispute between 1994 and 1996?", "answer": "Spain and Canada", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c26", "question": "Michael Jackson was called the King of what?", "answer": "Pop", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7d9", "question": "On what namesake Asian island were the first Homo erectus fossils found?", "answer": "Java", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339991", "question": "In the movie \"Ferris Bueller\u2019s Day Off\", what was Ferris\u2019 girlfriend\u2019s first name?", "answer": "Sloan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd31", "question": "Which Internet personality used the catchphrase, \"I remember it, so you don't have to!\"", "answer": "The Nostalgia Critic", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9c8", "question": "Which US state has the least rainfall?", "answer": "Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5909cd88bb53d1af658864e9", "question": "What spiced wine is traditionally consumed during the winter months, and especially around Christmas?", "answer": "Mulled wine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1c5", "question": "Who had a No.1 hit song in 1998 with \"C'est la Vie\"?", "answer": "B*Witched", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea793aff048f679a45abe0", "question": "What nerve tissue transmits light signals from your eye lens to the brain?", "answer": "Retina", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8cd", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Mastering the Art of French Cooking\"?", "answer": "Julia Child", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b68b", "question": "\"Lorgnette\" is the proper term for a pair of glasses with what?", "answer": "A handle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a893", "question": "What city is home to the Shukhov Tower?", "answer": "Moscow", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59a7f6806f5f79087132fb44", "question": "Mount Elbrus is the highest mountain in which country?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c652", "question": "What sense is most closely linked to memory?", "answer": "Smell", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beea", "question": "Electric, Perse and smalt are shades of which color?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c879", "question": "In computer science, what is a group of four bits called?", "answer": "A nibble", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b571b6667df192a942e3368", "question": "What is the capital of Nicaragua?", "answer": "Managua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3b1", "question": "In 1975, what re-opened after an 8 year closure?", "answer": "Suez Canal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60136f891381754895396378", "question": "What superhero uses a device called \"The Cosmic Treadmill\"?", "answer": "Flash -- The Cosmic Treadmill is used to help the Flash amplify his already considerable powers.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c850", "question": "In what organ of the human body would you find the alveoli?", "answer": "The lungs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339283", "question": "Who won part 1 of the final \"Head Of Household\" competition in season 14 of the TV show \"Big Brother\"?", "answer": "Dan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a73", "question": "Shoes worn by ballerinas are also called what?", "answer": "Pointe shoes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59071cb03745b36be73039cf", "question": "In what present-day country was the first space launch facility located?", "answer": "Kazakhstan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ee", "question": "What organization in the Harry Potter series is named after Dumbledore's patronus?", "answer": "Order of the Phoenix", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea36a2ff048f679a45ab10", "question": "What animal is sometimes used by museums to clean skeletons for display?", "answer": "Beetles", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea3ddbff048f679a45ab54", "question": "What's another name for vitamin B5", "answer": "Pantothenic Acid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac26", "question": "Which country borders Suriname to the east?", "answer": "French Guiana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe12e8ce39efa6330e0fed3", "question": "What is the oldest operating amusement park in the U.S.?", "answer": "Lake Compounce Amusement Park, Connecticut", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c00a", "question": "Strine is the vernacular language spoken in which country?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf6", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"A Death in the Family\"?", "answer": "James Agee", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8c8", "question": "How many pounds of jet fuel does a passenger Boeing 747 use during take off?", "answer": "Almost 6,000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a40", "question": "In 2000, the Black Crowes released a live album recorded with what legendary guitar player?", "answer": "Jimmy Page", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bfdfffcb668d7dfe168b5be", "question": "Who declined a Pulitzer Prize for his book \"Arrowsmith\"?", "answer": "Sinclair Lewis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c51", "question": "Who starred in the lead male role in the 1968 movie \"Planet of the Apes\"?", "answer": "Charlton Heston", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339264", "question": "What three letter name did the band formerly known as \"Slut Bank and Twisted Kites\" finally settle on?", "answer": "R.E.M.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad9df61e748bb36357acde8", "question": "The City of Hot Coffee is in what US state?", "answer": "Mississippi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59a1a1c612f2a7826b9b8715", "question": "What milk is Pecorino cheese made from?", "answer": "Ewe's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5cd", "question": "In the game \"Battleship\", how many hits does it take to sink an aircraft carrier?", "answer": "5", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600a2704e958e8c9f3127313", "question": "Where did the Mayflower land in New England in 1620?", "answer": "Cape Cod - The Mayflower sailed from England to the \u201cNew World,\u201d landing in Plymouth Harbor along the shores of Cape Cod.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f3b", "question": "What two long-running 1980s TV shows featured characters called Uncle Jesse?", "answer": "The Dukes of Hazzard and Full House", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339215", "question": "Who voiced Rocky in the movie \"Chicken Run\"?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909d267bb53d1af65886509", "question": "Candy canes are said to have originated from which European country?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ad2", "question": "What word comes from the Greek for \"thick-skinned\"?", "answer": "Pachyderm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8ab3d01dd7bf43be5e765", "question": "The Danish concept \"hygge\", often used in Scandinavian design, means what?", "answer": "Coziness and comfort", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f23aff048f679a45aab7", "question": "What was the title of Charles Darwin's influential book on evolution?", "answer": "\"On the Origin of Species\"", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad7d", "question": "Which enemy of the Roman Empire was nicknamed the \"Scourge of God\" by the Catholic Church?", "answer": "Attila the Hun", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389cf", "question": "What book of short stories has a second section called \"Kaa's Hunting\"?", "answer": "The Jungle Book", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133926d", "question": "Which rap star was born Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.?", "answer": "Snoop Dogg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133add3", "question": "How much did the United States pay Russia for the state of Alaska?", "answer": "$7.2 million", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc57", "question": "What is the literal translation of the dish \"Pad Thai\"?", "answer": "Fried Thai style", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba2e", "question": "What valley holds the record for the highest temperature recorded on American soil?", "answer": "Death Valley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59412802bab1e6f9796f1b59", "question": "In which card game might you be dealt a \"Yarborough\" hand?", "answer": "Bridge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b51d", "question": "What are the two basic types of Scotch Whisky?", "answer": "Single Malt and Single Grain", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1f8", "question": "Who chose her new name in 1953 to honor a Danish surgeon named Christian Hamburger?", "answer": "Christine Jorgensen", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b91d", "question": "The Stanley Cup is played for in what sport?", "answer": "Ice hockey", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8a7", "question": "Which element of the periodic table is named for a Scottish village?", "answer": "Strontium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133961d", "question": "Who starred as Connor Macleod in the 1986 movie \"Highlander\"?", "answer": "Christopher Lambert", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c3e97a9ebfabb9c85d8a965", "question": "Which popular beverage's name is German for \"storeroom\"?", "answer": "Lager", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ce2", "question": "At what US city did Bugs Bunny traditionally lament taking a left \"toin\"?", "answer": "Albuquerque", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8aad401dd7bf43be5e762", "question": "Which Thanksgiving favorite did Marcus L. Urann invent?", "answer": "Cranberry sauce", "category": "general"}]